<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" 
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" 
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Omar&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Omar&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</webMaster>
    <copyright>©{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:03:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    

      
      <item>
        <title>thefuck Imp Error</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/thefuck-imp-error/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:03:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/thefuck-imp-error/</guid>
        <description>After upgrading WSL2 to 24.04 Noble, thefuck stopped working with the error ModuleNotFoundError: No module named &#39;imp&#39;. It&amp;rsquo;s a known issue that stems from thefuck using a very deprecated Python package. Ubuntu in 24.04 now uses Python 3.12 which has removed that package, causing thefuck to break. You can&amp;rsquo;t pip install the latest version either, as you get an error about Python being &amp;ldquo;externally managed&amp;rdquo; now. So the fix is to use pipx to install thefuck into a virtualenv that uses Python 3.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Updating WSL2 to Noble</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/updating-wsl2-to-noble/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:40:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/updating-wsl2-to-noble/</guid>
        <description>Running my WSL2 on Ubuntu 22.04 Jammy Jellyfish, and wanted to update to 24.04 Noble Numbat.
Make sure we&amp;rsquo;re up to date
sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt full-upgrade Close terminal, quit Docker Desktop In PowerShell:
wsl -l -v (make sure we know what our Linux is called, probably Ubuntu)
wsl --terminate Ubuntu (took a few tries / waiting a bit, make sure it says stopped) Open a terminal, which will restart Ubuntu</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Raspberry Pi 2 Rainbow Screen</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/raspberry-pi-2-rainbow-screen/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:56:07 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/raspberry-pi-2-rainbow-screen/</guid>
        <description>I have a Raspberry Pi 2 Model B that I use for my WireHole setup. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty aged at this point and sort of fails whenever I try to update it. Oftentimes SSH just stops randomly working entirely until I update sshd, but doing a general system upgrade causes the device to fail to boot properly. I get stuck with a rainbow screen on boot and it continues to not respond to SSH.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Syncing Only .plexmatch Files</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/syncing-only-plexmatch-files/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:05:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/syncing-only-plexmatch-files/</guid>
        <description>The file syncing application I use to sync between my local data and my NAS (probably wisely) skips files that start with a . but I want my .plexmatch files to sync to my NAS too. I could remove this exception but I figured it&amp;rsquo;s probably best to not worry about that. I decided to sync them directly with rsync. Below is a method to sync all the files from all the subdirectories that match your input.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Plex Not Detecting Subtitles</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/plex-not-detecting-subtitles/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:00:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/plex-not-detecting-subtitles/</guid>
        <description>I noticed a whole season of one of my shows didn&amp;rsquo;t have subtitles on Plex. This is odd because every other season did, so I went to check the actual folders. All of the subtitles were there, and were actually named correctly too. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure why they weren&amp;rsquo;t showing up in Plex, so I renamed the files from ...en.srt to just ...srt and they showed up. This was even more odd because there weren&amp;rsquo;t any issues with any other subtitles named that way, so I renamed them back.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Nginx Proxy Manager Update Broke</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/nginx-proxy-manager-update-broke/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 21:46:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/nginx-proxy-manager-update-broke/</guid>
        <description>While back I updated my nginx-proxy-manager container and it broke, throwing an error message similar to this:
[nginx ] nginx: [emerg] cannot load certificate &amp;quot;/etc/letsencrypt/live/npm-3/fullchain.pem&amp;quot;
If you google around you can find this GitHub issue about the problem, that suggests your certs are lost forever if you didn&amp;rsquo;t have the folder set as a volume or have a backup. I do actually have the folder as a local folder mounted as a volume, so I was confused about why I was seeing the error when all my certs were there.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>WireGuard Reverse Proxy Issues</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/wireguard-reverse-proxy-issues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 21:04:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/wireguard-reverse-proxy-issues/</guid>
        <description>I use WireGuard (as part of WireHole) to allow my mobile devices to access my internal network when I&amp;rsquo;m not at home. I use an nginx reverse proxy container so I can use hostnames and SSL to access all my internal services, but some of these are public services and some of them are private.
I have all the hostnames registered with my registrar, and I have the private ones set up with private IPs for the A record.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Docker Desktop Stuck Stopping</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/docker-desktop-stuck-stopping/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:55:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:20:45 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/docker-desktop-stuck-stopping/</guid>
        <description>I use Docker Desktop with WSL2 on my Windows computer. Some days when Docker Desktop tries to update or I have some other issue with it, it gets stuck stopping even after killing the associated processes in task manager. I would restart Docker Desktop and it would still say &amp;ldquo;Docker Desktop stopping.&amp;rdquo;
The way I fixed it was:
Make sure Docker Desktop is totally stopped. Stop the app, kill the processes, everything Open powershell (my notes say I did this in an admin console but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to be admin) wsl --shutdown wsl --unregister docker-desktop wsl --unregister docker-desktop-data Then start Docker Desktop again and let it start WSL etc This worked for me but there&amp;rsquo;s a big caveat I think, the Microsoft docs have this :</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Metal Gear Solid RetroArch Settings</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/metal-gear-solid-retroarch-settings/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:21:40 -0500</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 01:44:13 -0500</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/metal-gear-solid-retroarch-settings/</guid>
        <description>I recently played through Death Stranding and loved it so much I decided to check out the rest of Kojima&amp;rsquo;s famous work. Unfortunately Konami has made it pretty difficult to enjoy the entire Metal Gear series on modern systems. All the games are available, but usually not in the same package, none are on PS4, and the recent GOG PC releases are apparently the original not-great releases. There&amp;rsquo;s an HD collection on the PS3, that I planned on playing via PS Now (can&amp;rsquo;t stream PS3 without an HDCP stripper, which I&amp;rsquo;m not about to buy) but that starts with MGS2 for some reason.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Windows Bootloader Issue</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/windows-bootloader-issue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:27:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 07:39:40 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/windows-bootloader-issue/</guid>
        <description>over the past day i swapped my computer case to a new one. its real shiny and nice (fractal define 7, all white)
it was a real PITA to put together because i have so many hard drives, i had to configure the case (which is modular and nearly fully disassemblable) into &amp;ldquo;storage mode&amp;rdquo; which involves taking apart most of the case and putting it back together differently. i also had issues following a lot of the instructions since i was trying probably too hard to plan ahead and make sure cable management would be easy and good when i was done</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Currently Playing Stack</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/currently-playing-stack/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 02:06:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:51:24 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/currently-playing-stack/</guid>
        <description>here&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;stack&amp;rdquo; of my currently playing (single-player or story) games, most current on top
this way i can try to make sure i finish what im in the middle of before i start too many other games
Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater Pokemon Violet No Man&amp;rsquo;s Sky Guild Wars 2 (Janthir Wilds) Higurashi When They Cry Shin Megami Tensei V Vengeance Opus Magnum Touhou Hero of Ice Fairy Nier Replicant Persona 3 Reload Unbeatable [white label] Hyper Light Drifter The Darkside Detective Death Stranding: Director&amp;rsquo;s Cut Rhythm Doctor Chrono Ark Final Fantasy VII Touhou Artificial Dream in Arcadia The Talos Principle Pikmin 4 Vampire: The Masquerade &amp;ndash; Night Road Super Mario RPG: Legend of the Seven Stars Fire Emblem: The Blazing Blade Marvel&amp;rsquo;s Spider-Man: Miles Morales The Legend of Zelda: Skyward Sword Metroid: Dread The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles Persona 5 Strikers Star Wars: Squadrons Cosmic Star Heroine Persona 4 Golden Half-Life: Alyx Doom: Eternal Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order Luigi&amp;rsquo;s Mansion 3 Monster Hunter World: Iceborne Resident Evil 2: (Second story, Leon) Earthbound </description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Discord Streamer</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/discord-streamer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 19:24:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:43:27 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/discord-streamer/</guid>
        <description>i wanted to stream SGDQ into a discord voice channel over the course of the week without needing to keep my desktop on. tried doing it with laptop but it was so chuggy
what i ended up doing was
get a g2.2xlarge windows instance on aws.
rdp in to the instance from my laptop log in, get twitch desktop app, log in, get discord desktop app, log in.
enable audio in rdp settings to play on the local computer</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>My third Post</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/test-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 23:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 03:06:04 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/test-post/</guid>
        <description>testing 3
Some third party entries in your sources.list were disabled. You can
re-enable them after the upgrade with the &amp;lsquo;software-properties&amp;rsquo; tool
or your package manager.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>embedded tracker</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/embedded-tracker/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 03:06:04 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/embedded-tracker/</guid>
        <description>create the tracker with your public ip and port as the tracker url, but then once youre seeding, change the tracker url locally to your local ip. then it should connect.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>My First Post</title>
        <link>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/my-first-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <author>ofsaleem@gmail.com (omar saleem)</author>
        <atom:modified>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 21:12:09 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>http://ofsaleem.me/en/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
        <description>i am a cow
i am not a cat
moo im a cow</description>
        
        <dc:creator>omar saleem</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
        
        
      </item>
      

    
  </channel>
</rss>